(Amy:)Make a baby?
What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)Clearly the combination
of our DNA is exceptional.
Eh... Our child could be
the next step
(Sheldon:)in the evolution of mankind.
We... we'll be able to get
into any preschool we want!
Sh-Sheldon, I'm not ready
to have a baby.
Oh, yes, you are!
I track your cycle.
(Sheldon:)For the next 36 hours
you're as fertile
(Sheldon:)as a manure-covered wheat field.
Wow. I-I can actually feel
(Amy:)the egg crawling its way
back up.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)I thought you'd be thrilled
to procreate with me.
(Amy:)Not right now.
Oh,
(Sheldon:)I see what's happening here.
(Sheldon:)You're playing hard to get.
(Amy:)I'm not playing anything.
(Amy:)We're not making a baby today.